<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yutong Wang</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yutong Wang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description>Hello! Hallo! 你好！
I&amp;rsquo;m a second year graduate student in Graduate Group of Biostatistics, at University of California, Berkeley, working in Prof. Yun S. Song&amp;rsquo;s group. I am broadly interested in statistical machine learning, causal inference and transfer learning, with applications in scRNA-seq and microbiome.
Feel free to contact me: ytwang at berkeley dot edu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/education/</guid>
      <description>Graduate Coursework:
Robust Statistics in High Dimensions, Theoretical Statistics, Advanced topics in Causal Inference, Probabilistic Modeling in Genomics, Statistical Models: Theory and Application I, II, Computational Statistics with Applications in Biology and Medicine
Undergraduate Coursework:
Functional Analysis, PDE, ODE, Real Analysis, Complex Analysis, Abstract Algebra, Stochastic Process, Probability, Mathematical Statistics, Statistical Inference, Optimization Methods, Modern Data Mining, Data Analytics &amp;amp; Statistical Computing, Computer Methods with Mathematical Science, C++, Advanced Calculus, Advanced Algebra, Analytical Geometry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misc</title>
      <link>/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/misc/</guid>
      <description>I used to work as a volunteer journalist in the New Citizen Program in China to raise the sexual health awareness of the public, left-behind children in particular. I later realized credible statistics of domestic sexual crime is impossibly difficult to collect in my home country. Thus I&amp;rsquo;ve been consistently interested in data collection and statistical analysis of related social issues for the sake of public policy-making.
I have published several articles in Chinese as a journalist, Here are some excerpts from my previous work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Under construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Fall 2018 - Spring 2019: Introduction to Statistics (Stat 2), with Professor Cari Kaufman  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>